PATRICK V. TIOTANGCO

4323 Water Lily Loop #102 Bellingham, WA 98226 · 425-458-8328 patricktiotangco@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/patrick-tiotangco-4b4913154

Highly motivated computer support specialist experienced in solving computer and operating system problems. Goal focused and diligent IT intern excels in collaborating with technology specialist to assist project management. Supports IT team members in ascertaining optimum policies to secure sensitive information. Highly effective at problem solving and decision making. Less than 1 year of progressive IT experience.

SKILLS

- Project coordination
- Networking background
- Technical troubleshooting
- Infrastructure maintenance
- Hardware installations
- Equipment set-up

EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2019 – FEBRUARY 2020

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN INTERN, MICROK12, LYNNWOOD, WA.

- Adhered to safety protocols and policies to reduce workplace hazards.
- Efficiently troubleshoot and repaired Laptop equipment to cut company costs and maximize productivity.
- Evaluated systems according to predetermined checklist and noted issues.
- o Gained knowledge of standard equipment, including manufacturer repair guidelines.
- O Documented all changes and actions in computer-based tracking system.
- O Demonstrated increased knowledge of company products and equipment.
- Diagnosed Lenovo Laptops and troubleshoot problems, repairing and restoring machines to peak performance.
- Used a ticketing system when working with laptops to record what was done to fix them.
- Experienced with shipping parts back to the vendor and third-party companies.

JULY 2019- SEPTEMBER 2019 SANITATION WORKER, VALET WASTE, BOTHELL, WA.

O Collected, sorted and disposed of garbage and recycling from production work areas.

SEPTEMBER 2016- JANUARY 2017 GRILL COOK, HOT IRON MONGOLIAN GRILL, SMOKEY POINT, WA

- Prepared food items such as meats, poultry and fish for frying purposes.
- o Grilled meats and seafood to customers specifications.
- Checked each food item for freshness and provided feedback to kitchen.
- O Cleaned and maintained kitchen equipment regularly.

EDUCATION

DECEMBER 2019

ASSOCIATE IN TECHNICAL ARTS- INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

EVERETT COMMUNITY COLLEGE

AWARDS AND HONORS

CompTIA IT Fundamental certification MTA: Mobility and Device Fundamentals

MTA: Networking Fundamentals MTA: Security Fundamentals

MTA: Windows Server Administration Fundamentals

CompTIA A+

LPI: Linux Essentials